<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-12T20:37:01-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Temporarily Unnamed</title><subtitle>A blog where I post whatever I feel like posting, idk</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Is Brookelyn Always Right?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jokes/2021/12/12/brookelyn-is-always-right.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is Brookelyn Always Right?" /><published>2021-12-12T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-12-12T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jokes/2021/12/12/brookelyn-is-always-right</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jokes/2021/12/12/brookelyn-is-always-right.html">&lt;p&gt;The premise of this post is simple: a fake card was cut saying that Brookelyn is always right, so I suppose it should have a dumb blog post to go with it ¯\_ (ツ)_/¯&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-does-it-mean-to-be-right&quot;&gt;What Does it Mean to be Right?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;correctness&quot;&gt;Correctness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being right can have several interpretations. It can mean that you are correct about something, i.e., your statements or actions consist of the absence of being wrong. We will use the age old example of pineapple on pizza to explain this. If I offered you Hawaiian Pizza and Pepperoni Pizza and asked you to choose, you would only be &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; if you picked the Hawaiian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;politics&quot;&gt;Politics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being right can also be viewed through a political context. If I say that I am a right leaning person, that means that I agree with portions of right-wing politics. Wikipedia defines right-wing politics as thus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Right-wing politics supports the view that certain social orders and hierarchies are inevitable, natural, normal, or desirable, typically supporting this position on the basis of natural law, economics, or tradition. Hierarchy and inequality may be seen as natural results of traditional social differences or competition in market economies. Right-wing politics are considered the counterpart to left-wing politics, and the left–right political spectrum is one of the most widely accepted political spectrums.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This alternate defenition of the word “right” now gives us even more to play with. A right leaning person then could say that the &lt;em&gt;right is right&lt;/em&gt;. If, say, the Republicans were pushing a bill to lower taxes and one agreed with it then they could say that is some &lt;em&gt;right right&lt;/em&gt;, adding a good portion of confusion into the mix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A left leaning person could further complicate things, as they now view the right as being wrong. Now we will have phrases such as, “&lt;em&gt;Right is wrong,&lt;/em&gt;” flying around, with little to no ability to evaluate these based on the original word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;throwing-hands&quot;&gt;Throwing Hands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sides of things are given names as well, as they now give us a third meaning of right. Some people are right handed and others are left handed. We use these directions for all sorts of things, such as the age old saying of &lt;em&gt;Righty Tighty, Lefty, Loosy&lt;/em&gt;. This adds more variation to what is right. If I want to put a screw into a board, then right is right. On the other hand (quite litteraly) if I want to take said screw out then the right is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what, lets talk about hands. As little kids we are taught to differentiate left and right using our hands. One simply makes two fists, puts out their index and thumb fingers, and the one that makes an L is the left hand, and the other is the right.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/brookelyn_is_right/left_right.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But using hands in such a way only complicates matters, as I can just flip one hand over suddenly left becomes right. Now everything is right, meaning that everything is correct and I am justified in anything that I want to do.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/brookelyn_is_right/right_right.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we flipped a different hand over then right would be left and nothing would be right and now there is never a correct choice and all morality or logic dies a painful death.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/brookelyn_is_right/left_left.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, if we flip both hands then left is right and right is left and now all we though was good is bad and bad is good and the structure of the universe begins to collapse.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/brookelyn_is_right/right_left.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-brookelyn-always-right&quot;&gt;Is Brookelyn Always Right?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we went through that entire mess, we need to answer the question, “Is Brookelyn always right?” The answer to that is simple: &lt;strong&gt;No&lt;/strong&gt;. Brookelyn is a mere mortal like the rest of us, and I recall that there was a rumor that she messed up at something like 6 years ago, though I’m not sure what. In any case, that means that the fake card mentioned above was powertagged, which is kinda sad but alright then&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jokes" /><summary type="html">The premise of this post is simple: a fake card was cut saying that Brookelyn is always right, so I suppose it should have a dumb blog post to go with it ¯\_ (ツ)_/¯ What Does it Mean to be Right? Correctness Being right can have several interpretations. It can mean that you are correct about something, i.e., your statements or actions consist of the absence of being wrong. We will use the age old example of pineapple on pizza to explain this. If I offered you Hawaiian Pizza and Pepperoni Pizza and asked you to choose, you would only be right if you picked the Hawaiian.</summary></entry></feed>